3 Shannondale Court Fredericksburg VA 22406 August 14, 2020

Booze Allen Hamilton 475 Aquia Town Center Drive Suite 201 Stafford, VA 22554

Dear Recruiter or whom it may concern,

I am applying for the position of Data Analyst from the job requisition at Quantico, VA, which is advertised on LinkedIn Jobs as of August 1st, 2020.

As an undergraduate student at George Mason University, I will be completing a Bachelor of Science in Computational and Data Sciences with a minor in Computer Game Design in December 2020. During my time at George Mason University, I had the privilege of working on multiple projects using R, Python, Fortran, and other programming languages in addition to Tableau, Visual Studio, as well as other data science tools. Coming from a family that has many connections with federal contractors, the prospect of working at a federal contractor has been engrained in me for quite some time. I am currently under investigation by the federal government to receive a TS SCI clearance.

In the past year, I have worked with companies involved in government contracting as well as the health care sector, so I am no stranger to information on a need-to-know basis. I have been working on my skills in data science to create visualizations and simulations/modeling. I have also been completing research on some ocean and space related topics, of which you can see on my resume.

Enclosed is my current resume for your consideration. I would greatly appreciate meeting to discuss the full details of the position. I can be reached at my phone number 571-428-3545 or by email at either rcpayung@gmail.com or rpayung@gmu.edu. I look forward to your response.

Sincerely,

Riley Payung

Riley C. Payung

rcpayung@gmail.com | rpayung@gmu.edu +1-(571)-428-3545

Professional Summary

Over the past few years, I have worked on many projects involving visual/data analytics, software engineering, and research. My background in computer science has helped me tremendously in these endeavors. As can be seen below, I have experience with programming in multiple languages and software packages. I am looking forward to a future in software engineering or data analytics.

Education

George Mason University

Computational and Data Sciences, B.S.

Minor in Computer Game Design

Fall 2016 – Fall 2020 Fairfax, Virginia

- Worked on multiple projects regarding modeling/simulation and visual analytics
- Language Packages: C/C++, Java, Python, JavaScript, Fortran, SQL, PHP, R
 - Software: Tableau, Anaconda/Jupiter Labs, Microsoft VSC, R-Studio, Eclipse
 - Python: Pandas, Matplotlib, NetworkX, Numpy
 - o C/C++: SDL2, Boost, RapidXML
- Attempted startup Game Dev Share, an online job/marketplace website (See GitHub)
- Research on image processing in spatial imagery and ocean-bound plastics pollution

Annandale High School

Fall 2012 – Spring 2016 Annandale, Virginia

- Advanced Mathematics and Sciences Credits
- Varsity Swim and Dive

Experience

Data Science & IT Intern Cardiology Associates of Fredericksburg January 2020 – Current Fredericksburg, Virginia

- Administration of Windows Servers
- Worked on upgrading enterprise health suite NextGen. Usability testing to ensure templates were viable on new version as well as beta-testing new templates.
- Asset Tagging and Inventory

Data Science Intern
Innovative Management and Technology
Approaches

May 2019 – January 2020 May 2017 – September 2017 Arlington, Virginia

- Wrote requirements, programming, and established proprietary business intelligence application built in SharePoint.
- Migration of data to SharePoint.

- Presented certification requirements for CMMI-SVC L3, ISO 20000, 27001, and CMMC certs to company executives to maintain respective certifications.
- Upgrade of administrative firewall to SonicWall TZ500 W.
- Destruction of data-sensitive drives along with barcode capture.
- DLA EPoS Usability testing on \$150M military logistics fueling product.

Assistant Manager Annandale Swim and Tennis

May 2013 – September 2018 Annandale, Virginia

• Lifeguarded, some payroll responsibilities, and scheduling of employees. Previously held CPR/AED certification.

Volunteer Experience

Owen Lea Foundation https://www.owenleafoundation.org

2019 – Current

Fredericksburg, Virginia

• Volunteer in Fundraising activities for Neuroblastoma.

Food for Others https://www.foodforothers.org

2012 – 2016 Mclean, Virginia

• Volunteered in creating packages of food.